MANYU LAKHOTIA

+1(337)322-4192 \$\times LakeMonYew@gmail.com \$\times portfolio.majorziploc.com www.linkedin.com/in/majorziploc/ \sigma github.com/MajorZiploc \sigma majorziploc.itch.io/

Software Developer with 8+ years of work experience in developing web applications, stand alone applications, cicd, and databases; along with personal experience in art/design, scripting, web scraping, gamedev, data analytics, and data cleaning.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend react, redux, iguery, css, sass, html, material ui, bootstrap, krita, inkscape, winforms, cypress.io

Backend/Testing/Headless django, express, nodejs, asp.net mvc, google app suite, jest, pandas, webscraper.io, tampermonkey

Languages javascript, python, typescript, bash, sql, mongodb, php, redis, java, C#, F#, powershell, rbql, vimscript

DevOps docker, aws, kubernetes, gitlab ci, github actions, ansible, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity, vmware

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8

New York, NY

Feb 2024 - Present

Optimal Dynamics

(Logistics)

• Mapping: consume data from many customers in many formats to a unified format for processing

- Discovery: Undertook greenfield development and research to scout new projects
- Utilized: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8 Conservis (Agriculture)

May 2022 - Jan 2024 Minneapolis, MN

- SOC2: Improved authentication by moving from homebrewed auth solution to keycloak
- Design: Use krita and inkscape to design frontend mockups and create svg icons
- Utilized: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

Software Developer - Full time - Mostly Remote - Team size: 4-10

Mar 2020 - Apr 2022

Acadian Ambulance

Lafayette, LA

- Leadership: Led development of an ambulance scheduling system
- Testing: Introduced automated UI and API testing using Cypress.io
- Utilized: F#, C#, react, redux, wsl, mssql, docker, just, bash, microservices, aws, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity

Software Developer - Part time - Remote - Team size: 3-5 Cythereal (Cyber security)

Jun 2021 - Apr 2022

Lafayette, LA

- Visualization: Created dashboard to investigate potential malware samples
- Utilized: django, react, redux, docker, mongodb, redis, rpm, bash, azure, ansible, terraform, packer, just

Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 10-15 CGI (Medical)

Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Lafayette, LA

- Modernization: Migrated legacy health insurance portal to more modern solutions
- Utilized: django, react, redux, docker, redis, mongodb, bash, openshift, vscode

Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 4-6

Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

Lafayette, LA

Wetlands Research Center (Aquaculture)

Processing: Developed a stand alone java swing app for analyzing geospatial water levels from large NetCDF files

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

F# projects with contributions FSharpPlus, Acadian.FSharp, Acadian.Dapper.Fs, Acadian.Json.Fs (Available on nuget)

keycloak A oauth2 library with user federations, management and more (Available on maven) (java)

nvim-dev-container A nvim plugin for remote devcontainers using same configs as vscode devcontainers (lua)

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Economics with Computer Science and Mathematics, University of Louisiana at Lafayette

2016 - 2018

Associates in General Studies Business, South Louisiana Community College

2013 - 2015